<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>闲聊 - 分类 - 無糖的小宇宙</title>
        <link>https://sugarless.cn/categories/%E9%97%B2%E8%81%8A.html</link>
        <description>闲聊 - 分类 - 無糖的小宇宙</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><managingEditor>jaded@foxmail.com (無糖)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>jaded@foxmail.com (無糖)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sugarless.cn/categories/%E9%97%B2%E8%81%8A.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>About blog</title>
    <link>https://sugarless.cn/posts/en/about.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
        <name>無糖</name>
    </author><guid>https://sugarless.cn/posts/en/about.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>About Content and Tools</p>
<p>I&rsquo;ve been trying to use some note taking software for about half a year now, and I&rsquo;ve gradually fallen into the swamp of searching and experiencing all kinds of note taking software, which seems to be a strange circle that shouldn&rsquo;t exist: looking for a note taking app, experiencing it, and looking for the next note taking app, but we shouldn&rsquo;t be like this, originally wanting to find a good weapon to fight with, but finally becoming a shopkeeper of a weapon store.</p>
<p>Recently gradually realized, should gradually return to the original heart, think of what content, find the right place to start writing immediately, the content is far more important than the carrier.</p>
<p>No longer go to spend a lot of time looking for good tools, focus on content output, improve their own, obviously more important.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>关于博客</title>
    <link>https://sugarless.cn/posts/about.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><author>
        <name>無糖</name>
    </author><guid>https://sugarless.cn/posts/about.html</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>关于内容和工具。</p>
<p>大概在半年前，尝试并且使用了一些笔记软件，于是逐渐陷入寻找的沼泽里，一发不可收拾，开始体验各种笔记软件，这似乎是陷入了一个不应该存在的怪圈：找笔记APP，体验，找下一个笔记APP。而我们本心不该是这样的，本来是想找个称手的兵器打仗，最后却变成了武器商店的店长。</p>
<p>近期逐渐意识到了，应该逐渐回归初心，想到什么内容，就找合适的地方马上开始写，内容远比载体重要的多。</p>
<p>不再去把大量的时间花在寻找好工具上了，专注于内容产出，提升自己，显然更加重要。</p>]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
